brigita At Your
Service Bastion how are you liking that
new armor Papa Made For
You Genji how about a quick sparring
session you're on show me what you've
been working
on believe me I I get wanting to wear
the armor and all but following the old
man around must be nothing but trouble I
don't see it that way to me it's an
honor Angela it's so strange to see you
in your armor I could say the same for
you I'm really looking forward to
fighting with you far we OverWatch brats
have to stick
together Pita I'd love it if you could
take a look at my armor sometime it'll
take some time for me to get familiar
with the design but if you don't mind
I'd love
to did you ever want to join OverWatch
growing up not after how they treated
Reinhardt he deserved
better hey brigita want to go hit the
weights you're
on hey Bita want to go hit the weights
only if we can get something to eat
afterwards Reinhard what should I focus
on today focus on offense drive your
enemy back with the blows from your
flail Reinhard what should I focus on
today your Shield keep yourself from
harm then bash it against our
enemies Reinhard what should I focus on
today protect your teammates make sure
they do not
falter Reinhard what should I focus on
today try to keep me out of
trouble Reinhard what should I focus on
today no lesson today show me what you
have
learned sure you don't want to sit this
one out Reinhardt you ask every time and
every time I say no today is no
different stay close to me of course how
else can I bail you out when you get
into
trouble I've stitched you up so many
times it's a wonder you can still fight
just some bumps and bruises nothing to
worry yourself
about you know I've seen reinhardt's
OverWatch file what are you getting at I
wander he's really told you the truth
about his
retirement Papa what do you think of my
armor not bad not bad I'm glad you let
me add a little something to it your
armor seems to be working well I guess
you were right about the core
integration design I knew you'd come
around why does everyone keep pestering
me about my arars it's true you have
been sucking off a bit lately
isn't it enough to be an engineer
brigita I felt like I had to do
more got you this time
Reinhardt sorry
Papa enemy turret ahead one of Papa's
beloved
Creations sorry Papa back to the scrap
peep